[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：还有一个攻击，并且
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: There's still one attack left, and
这是一次无序的攻击。
this one is an out of order attack.
攻击者可能导致的
That the attacker can cause
要在另一条消息之前传递的消息，至少要传递给某些订阅者。
a message to be delivered before another message, at least to some subscribers.
通过这样做，他可以在市场上制造混乱。
By doing so, he can create confusion in the marketplace.
你怎么做到的？
How do you do that?
&GT；&GT；扬声器2：你在学校做过，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You did this in school,
它应该在你的消息中才能成为订阅者。
should it in your messages in the order to be subscribers.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：每个订阅者都应该按照以下顺序获得它们
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Each of the subscribers should get them in the order that
订阅，他们也应该每个人
subscribed, and they should also each of them
应该按照消息发送的顺序获取消息。
should get the messages in the order that they are sent.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：有些订阅者是用这个号码订阅的吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And some subscribers subscribe with the number?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：不，这会导致抛出异常，并且
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, that would cause an exception to get thrown, and
我们已经忽略了这些。
we already ignored those.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：所以我们现在假设我们正在进行foreach
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So we're assuming at this point that we're working on the foreach
循环而不是以前的任一种，但不关注这一种。
loop rather than the previous either one, but not to focus on this one.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：你喜欢，因为我们可以看到
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You like, since we can see that the corrections that
到目前为止，我们已经修复了这个新的，如此多的推动。
we have made up to this point have fixed this new And so much of the push push on.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：很容易推动他们的功能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's very easy pushing their function
方法还是螺丝钉的顺序呢，颠倒了吗？
methods or screw with the order of it, reverse it?
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：不，你说的是我们做的第一个问题？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: No, you're talking about the first problem we did?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：是的，那个人使用了store，因为我们可以说出
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, and that one was using store, because we could name
它要去哪里，那就是我们没有提供这样做的API。
where it was going to go, and that's when we haven't provided an API for doing that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：明白。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Gotcha.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：这个结构的好处是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: And the good thing about this construction is that
这是不可能的，因为他们，嗯，这是我们修复的东西，
that's impossible because they, well, it's something that we fix the thing,
在那里他们可以访问订阅者或通过这个访问。
where they can get access to the subscribers or a through this.
他们无法向订阅者添加属性，除非通过
There is no way that they can add a property to subscribers except through
订阅功能。
the subscribe function.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不再可以访问这个，访问-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Doesn't have access to this anymore, to the-
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：正确。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: That's correct.
&gt；&gt；演讲者4：我们是想把消息弄乱还是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Are we trying to get the messages out of order or
订阅者出了问题？
the subscribers out of order?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：留言顺序错误。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: The message is out of order.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：设置超时。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Set time out.
是这样的，
Is and that would make,
它会改变你的想法。
it would change where yours comes in.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，settimeout可能是解决方案的一部分，但
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, settimeout might be part of the solution but
这不是问题的一部分。
it's not part of the problem.
&GT；&GT；演讲者2：你知道我们可能会等。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You know we might wait.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：我们不必在网站上等待。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We don't have to wait on the site.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你知道，那是因为它无论如何都是同步的，如果我们
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You know and that's because it's synchronous anyways if it works if we
只是把所有的东西都叫成实际的样子就行了。
just call everything just exactly as in effect.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：因为它停止一切准备。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: because it is it stops everything ready.
所以，是的，所以这不是这个的一部分
So yeah so that that's not part of this
您知道，每次您单击时，每当有人调用PUBLISH时
you know every time you click every time somebody calls publish
出版物就是这样的信息，对吗？
a publication is that's the message right?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：将通读订阅者和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is gonna read through the subscribers and
打给它，然后你说的是
call it and then what you're saying is
我叫它然后你在我之后叫它你是坏人
I call it and then you call it after me you're that you're in the bad guy
你用我的名字来称呼它，因为不知何故或者你的跳线在我的前面。
you call it after me because somehow or yours jumper wire infront of mine.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：这就是我们要找的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: That's what we're looking for.
但你不能叫它，直到它和我的结束，因为它是，
But you can't call it until it's finished with mine because it's,
这个过程是漫长的。
the process is long.
但那是错的。
But that wrong.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：我可以将pubsub对象传递给我的函数吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Can I pass in the pubsub object to my function?
然后在通话中重新订阅我自己。
and then resubscribe myself in the midst of a call.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：你很接近了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You're close.
不是那样的，但就是这样。
It's not quite like that but it's that kind of this.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：这是巨大的漏洞吗？不是因为这些
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is this a vulnerability in for huge not because these
只是一些传教士说的对。
are just some preachy Right.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：那么我们本质上是在创建一个无限循环吗
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So are we essentially creating an infinite loop
根据他说的话。
based on what he said.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我们不是在寻找
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We are not looking for
无限循环，因为无限循环将是拒绝服务攻击。
an infinite loop because an infinite loop would be a denial of service attack.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：有人可以做
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: And someone can do
一个无限循环而不调用我们的代码。
an infinite loop without calling our code.
他们可以把自己的代码放在无限循环中，所以
They can just sit in their own code into an infinite loop so
这不是这个代码可以防御的东西。
that that's not something this code can defend against.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：在forEach内部，可以更改s的值吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And inside of forEach, can you change the value of s?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以如果我发布一个对象，并且
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So if I publish one object, and
然后稍后发布另一个对象并
then later on, publish another object And
该分离对象在其中具有将Aspect设置为第一个对象的功能。
that separate object has a function in it that sets aspect to the first object.
这是一件肮脏的事吗。
Is that a nasty thing to do.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：嗯，这不太可能发生，因为无论你是什么功能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Well that's not likely to happen because whatever function you're
将要做的事情，将在范围之外创建，并且
going to be doing, that will be created outside of the scope and
所以看不到。
so will not see at.
是的，只有这个范围内的函数才能看到我们。
yeah only functions in this scope can see us.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：所以如果我通过了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So if I pass it.
弹出到我的订阅者功能
The pops up to my subscribers function
当调用我的函数时，我再次调用public。
when my function is called I call public Again.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And
我们重新开始循环。
we restart to loop in the beginning again.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：没错。&gt；&gt；演讲者3：我们继续做
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Exactly. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And we keep on doing
我们永远也得不到。
that we'll never get it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Right.
所以，这是一个俗气刚刚描述。
So, this is a tacky just describe.
因此，他订阅了一个函数，该函数将发布和
So, he subscribes a function Which will publish and
这个函数在发布循环中被调用，所以他可以剪切它。
this function gets called in the publication loop so he can cut it.
然后，他可以使他自己的消息发表，并
He can then cause his own message to get published and
发送给订阅者名单中的每个人
delivered to everybody who is after himself in the subscriber list
而在这样做的过程中，他会导致事情变得乱七八糟。
And in doing that, he causes things to go out of order.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：莱昂纳多在聊天室再次击败我们。\
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Leonardo in the chat room beat us again.\
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：莱昂纳多，干得好。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Way to go Leonardo.
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；扬声器4：好吧，文森特是第一个，
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Well Vincent was the first,
是的文森特上次打败了我们。
yeah Vincent beat us last time.
这次是列奥纳多。
This time it was Leonardo.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：你必须告诉我们这一点。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You need to be telling us that.
之前-&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我知道。
Before- &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I know.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我不知道它就像-&gt；&gt；扬声器2：他
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I didn't know it's like- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: He's
A&GT；&GT；扬声器4：是的。
a &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：好的，那么
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay, so
我使用我们昨天写的极限函数的原因。
the reason I used the limit function that we wrote yesterday.
因为如果我不这样做，那么我就是在制造拒绝服务攻击，对吧。
Because if I don't then I'm just creating a denial of service attack, right.
我们将一遍又一遍地递归地调用它。
We'll keep calling it over and over again recursively.
拒绝服务攻击并不能完成
And a denial of service attack doesn't accomplish
我们试图利用的安全漏洞，只是损害了一个系统。
the security exploit that we're trying to do, it just impairs a system.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：限制是我们昨天写的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A limit's what we wrote yesterday.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，我们昨天写了Limit，所以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah we wrote limit yesterday, so
这意味着当我接到电话时，我将发送一条消息。
that means when I get called I am going to send one message.
而且这个消息会比其他人先传递。
And that message will get delivered before everybody else.
那你怎么解决这个问题？
So how would you fix that?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：每次有人发布消息时。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: every time somebody publishes a message.
我的信息将会流传出去，它只会发生一次。
My message will go out it would only ever happen once.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：嗯，但我可以控制它，你知道这是最简单的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Well but I can control it you know this is the simplest
防止它变得被滥用的方法，但显然我们可以放一个更聪明的
way to keep it from getting Getting abusive but obviously we can put a smarter
函数，它可以在每次调用时更改其行为。
function in there that could change its behavior every time it's called.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：您可以取下订阅者，然后
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You could take off the subscriber and
确保它不是一个物体，对吗？
make sure it's not an object right?
在您推送之前，请先查看订阅者。
The subscriber before you push.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：不，订阅者实际上必须是，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: No, the subscribers have to be In fact,
这就是tri catch的用途，以保证它们是函数。
that's what the tri catch was for, to guarantee that they are functions.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
你能-&gt；&gt；演讲者2：你能暂时
Can you- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Would you just temporarily
将发布的值更改为其他值，但它被冻结了。
changed the value of publish to something else, but it's frozen.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：对我们，是的，我们解决了这个问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Right we, yeah we fixed that one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我只是在想一种禁用发布的方法
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I was just trying to think of a way to disable publish
在这个循环里面。
inside of this loop.
所以如果你刚开始，你可以，是的，
So if you just set, you could, yeah,
你在上面放了一个var，上面写着“发布关闭”(Publish Off)。
you put a var at the top of this that says publish off.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，我们可以在顶部放一个布尔值，表示，我们在
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, we could put a boolean up at the top which says, we're in
发布模式，因此当我们循环时，SUBSCRIBE或PUBLISH是关闭的。
the publication mode, so subscribe or publish is turned off while we're looping.
那肯定行得通。
That would certainly work.
我接近它的方式是，
The way I would approach it is,
我会做一个异步解决方案，因为我喜欢同步。
I would do an asynchronous solution because I like a synchrony.
所以浏览器、Java和节点中都有称为setTimeout的东西。
So there's something that's in browsers and in Java and in node called setTimeout.
setTimeout接收一个函数并
And setTimeout receives a function and
导致该函数在将来执行。
causes that function to get executed in the future.
你可以给它一个时间，表示从现在起不早于零毫秒
And you can give it a time which says no sooner than zero milliseconds from now
调用此函数。
call this function.
但这个功能发生在不同的转折中。
But this function happens in a different turn.
所以它会在当前所有的时间之后被安排好
So it'll get scheduled after all of the current
当前回合的工作已完成。
work in the current turn is finished.
所以这会导致。
So this would cause.
所有的东西都在计时器队列中排好队
Everything to get lined up in the timer queue and
那么如果有人想在发布期间订阅，
then if someone wants to subscribe during a publication,
他们的内容稍后将被添加到计时器队列中。
their stuff will get added later in the timer queue.
所以一切都保持有序，我们使用计时器队列对消息进行排序。
So everything stays in order, we're using the timer queue to sort the messages.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：现在，我们可以这样做。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Now, so we could do that.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：所以您将出版物移到一个单独的队列中
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So you move the publication off into a separate queue the one that
如果这里发生了什么就能独立处理吗？
gets processed independently if whatever goes on here?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：对，这也意味着我现在不需要在这里尝试接球，因为
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Right and it also means I don't need to try catch here now because
如果它失败了，那么在那个转弯中它就会失败。
If it fails it'll fail in that turn.
但是然后系统说，好吧，那就转到终点，然后继续下一个。
But then the system says, well that turns finish and will go on to the next one.
所以一切都在继续。
And so everything keeps going.
现在看来，这里面有一个危险，因为设计错误
Now it turns out there's one hazard in this because of the design error in
这种超时的工作方式当您暂停这样的超时，它会返回一个数字并
the way such a timeout works when you pause such timeout it returns a number And
你可以传递这个数字来清除超时，这样就可以防止事情发生。
you can pass that number to clear timeout and that'll prevent things from happening.
不幸的是，这是一个很容易猜测的数字。
Unfortunately, it is an easily guessable number.
这意味着如果攻击者能猜到下一步
And that means if the attacker can guess what the next
清除超时编号将是。
clear timeout number is going to be.
他可以阻止传递消息。
He can prevent messages from being delivered.
通过取消队列中的那些消息。
By cancelling those messages that are in the queue.
所以我们必须解决这个问题，但我们改天再解决这个问题。
So we would have to fix that but we'll fix that one another day.